

# JUNBEOM WOO

Frontend/Backend Developer || EU residence and work permit holder

Oambakken 3, 1, 3460 Birkerød, Denmark

iunbeom2.woo@gmail.com



+45 44 11 14 18



junbeomwooo

#### PROFILE INFO

I am 27 years old, I was born in South Korea and I currently reside in Denmark with my partner. I hold a residence permit under the EU regulations, which entitles me to live and work in Denmark. I have a bright and outgoing personality, I consider myself a fast-learner and I am passionate about web development. I have experience in working on projects in teams as well as individualy. As a personal project, I created a website for an imaginary e-shop Unico that showcases various skills I learned. I have a background in visual design and completed a 920 hour coding boot camp. I have improved my English skill through working and traveling in Canada for 6 months.

#### **EDUCATION**

## Ezen Academy, Full Stack(JavaScript) Web Developer (Front/BackEnd)

August 2022 - January 2023 (920hr / 115days)

#### Courses

- Front End Programming
- JavaScript Programming
- · Building a Developer Environment
- · Applied Programming
- Server Programming
- · Building a Linux Server System
- Bachelor of Visual Design, Jangan University, South Korea

March 2016 - February 2022

## Courses

- · Web Design · Brand Design · Editorial Design · Package Design
- · Advertisement Design
- · Character Design
- · Capstone Design
- · 3D Studio Design

## WORK EXPERIENCE

Customer Service at Seoul Koreansk BBQ, Denmark

November 2024 - Present

Information Desk duties at Lotte Department store, South Korea

October 2020 - February 2021

Customer Service at Cheongnyun Dining and Namu, Canada

November 2019 - April 2020

Customer Service at CJ Food Ville, South Korea

September 2018 - June 2019

SKILI	LO			
HTML 8	CSS		_	
JavaScr	ipt & Ty <sub>l</sub>	peScript		
			_	
React &	Next.js			
Node.js	& Expre	ess		
MySQL				
Git				
Adobe I	llustrato	or & Pho	toshop	
LANG	GUAG	SES -		
KOREA	N			
	—		—	
ENGLIS	Н			
DANUG				
DANISH	1			